You have five minutes.
Relieve yourselves.
Where is 0864?
0864!
Thought we'd leave without you?
You wouldn't last an hour out here.
The wolves will eat you alive.
I hate roommates.
We have something in common already.
Last guy made it a month.
I'll be here three days tops.
Everyone here is a lifer.
One minute longer.
you can take your best shot.
It's a deal.
Can I sit with you at lunch?
No.
This is a private area.
Fuck off.
Who the fuck do you think you are. asshole?
Now it's open territory.
Boss wants to see you.
So this is the man my men want to kill.
Do you know who I am?
You're Semyon Chorney.
You run the Kirov Gang.
Your guns kill thousands of men.
women and kids all over the world.
You know me.
Who the hell are you?
Me?
I'm a hunter.
He's a hunter.
What do you hunt?
People like you.
The Hunter is a myth.
Now you're trapped. hunter.
What's your name? Who sent you?
My name is...
Kraven.
Kraven?
But I'm sure you yvon't tell anyone.
There's an ounce of truth in every myth.
Prisoner escaping!
Three days.
He's getting away!
Move. move. move!
You are late.
Next time you break out
of prison and I fly this thing.
No thanks.
So. how did it go?
How it always goes.
Good for me.
Bad for him.
We've got a body over here.
Have you identified him yet?
It's prisoner 0864.
Then who the fuck killed Chorney?
16 YEARS EARLIER
ST. MICHAEL'S ACADEMY. UPSTATE NEW YORK
Kravinoff and Kravinoff.
your father is coming to pick you up.
What did you do?
Me? Nothing. I thought it was you.
No.
Where are we going. papa?
We are in the middle
of a term at school.
Sergei.
Mom never made us do shit like this.
Your mother is dead.
She took on life. She was weak.
Sick in her mind.
It was her choice.
Well. she died because
you sent her away.
No.
She gave up long ago.
You haven't even
seen her for two years.
Nothing will change for you.
Or for you. Dmitri.
Where are we going.
papa? To the funeral?
If you take on life. you
do not get honor of funeral.
So then where are you taking us?
We go to hunt.
There'll be new
sightings of lion. tsar.
It will be good for you.
Both.
To join men.
Be one with nature.
Shoot to kill.
Fun.
Careful with those.
Put the cards away now. Calypso.
Your mom and dad
will be back soon.
And you know the way
they feel about all this.
It's just a game. granny.
You think my cards
are just pretty pictures.
Think again. Calypso.
They show us the unseen road.
What? Like. predict the future?
In the right hands.
Lay three cards down.
The first card is the subject.
The high priestess?
You do come from a long
line of very powerful women.
The second card
is the situation.
The tower.
There's going to be
a terrible accident.
The third card is the outcome.
Strength.
There is great
danger in that card.
I have something
for you. Calypso.
I was going to wait until
you were older. but the
cards have shown us
you will need it very soon.
What is it?
A potion.
The formula has been passed
down in our family for generations.
What does that symbol mean?
It's a sign of the
spirit. Papa Legba.
He opens the gate
to the other side.
Protect it.
Very powerful.
Go ahead.
It will heal whoever drinks
it in undreamed of ways.
The time is coming soon.
You'll know what to do with it.
Now put those away
before your parents get back.
Well done. Nikolai!
Sergei.
You see?
So beautiful.
Never fear death.
They are prey.
We are predators.
Men should be only
animal that is dreaded.
Dmitri. don't look so weak.
Be a man.
You all right?
Yeah.
He shouldn't have talked to you like that.
Yeah. well...
he's an asshole.
There's nothing I
can do about that.
He'll never respect
me like he respects you.
Wanna bet?
I miss Mom.
Me too. Dima. Me too.
Is this the Tsar?
Not even pussycat.
Perhaps it's the Tsar's
illegitimate half-brother.
Like your Dmitri.
Leave the boy.
He carries no blame for
his father's wandering eyes.
You will know
Tsar when you hear.
His sound like thunder
from mountaintop.
You have seen this beast?
I have seen his work.
This cat has killed two dozen.
maybe three dozen men.
Yes?
For as long as men like you have
been coming down here to kill lions.
there have been legends of
the one who can't be killed.
Men like me?
But you still take my
money. don't you. Bahari?
A lion hunts for food.
Same as I do.
Why do you hunt. Nikolai?
You know this. Bahari.
Men who kill legend
becomes legend.
Nikolai. we should talk.
Save your breath.
No. it's a condition. I'll be okay as long
as I take a few breaks here and there.
One thing that you should know about me
is that I'm always thinking of the future.
I want you to be my partner.
What is your name?
I'm a guest here of Vladimir.
Alexey Sytsevitch.
No.
You do not have a name.
In this world. you barely exist.
So what can some
non-name. non-existent.
condition-suffering fool
offer up to the Kravinoff?
Nothing.
I am here teaching my
sons the joy of stalking.
And you and your imbecilic
voice are stalking me.
So be quiet.
I hope father gets him this time.
Why?
Because then he'll become a legend
and we don't have to come here again.
A true legend would
fight fair. not with a gun.
You do it one-on-one with
only the tools you were born with.
Dmitri. get back.
Dmitri. move! Move!
Run!
Sergei!
Calypso. look!
Come on. honey. stand up.
Calypso?
Calypso!
In the name of all the
spirits and all the mysteries...
Granny!
… bring the power of the earth.
Wait.
Bring the power of the stars.
Everybody's clear. Shocking now.
Okay. team. we've done all we
can. I'm going to call time of death.
Six-fifty-one.
The EMTs found that card in your
pocket. You are one very lucky boy.
Thank you for saving me.
I wish I could say I did.
But I didn't save you.
I don't understand.
That makes the two of
us. But we're going to run some tests.
see if we can figure out what happened.
Sergei.
Dima.
Why did you not shoot?
You must be Sergei's
father. Mr. Kravinoff.
I am here to take him home.
He needs to stay
here and recover.
Clinically. he was dead
for more than three minutes.
He will be leaving with me.
Sergei.
but we will be soon.
what I would have ever wanted.
but it is the only choice your father gave me.
you will never become a man like him.
Sergei! Come down here!
Father is the only
animal that is dreaded.
You're getting too good at that.
You'll be all right.
You almost got
your brother killed.
You almost got yourself killed.
Because you were afraid.
Fear will eat you.
It makes you weak.
Are you weak like
your mother? Crazy?
Or are you like me?
Because if you show weakness to
enemies. it gives them an opening.
You are old enough
to understand.
You know my business. yes?
One day. you will be in charge.
Dmitri. go!
Dmitri will go back
to school in New York.
And you will stay here with me.
I think America
is making you soft.
It is for your own good.
Each of us have a path to walk.
Embrace who you really are.
And you will have
the strength to walk it.
Come.
Come here.
I got you something.
You never have
to be afraid again.
He should have killed you!
What is going on with you?
Sergei! Get back here!
Are you okay?
Don't leave me with him.
I'm going. I have to.
Why?
I can't explain it. Something
has happened to me.
What are you talking about?
Do you remember the
place we used to camp?
All you could hear were
the crickets and the owls.
My mom used to sing
to us around the fire.
That land is all I
have left of her.
How does that make it okay?
Picture me there.
I'm sorry. Dima.
I am.
Just go if you're gonna go.
Go.
I won't be gone forever.
Where are you headed?
I'm trying to get out
of England. To Russia.
On this?
You know there's planes
and trains here. don't you?
Are you on the run?
Yes. I am.
Come on. Come on.
She was weak. Sick in her mind.
She died because
you sent her away.
Sergei!
Run!
Fear will eat you.
It makes you weak.
Each of us has a path to walk.
They are prey.
We are predators.
Just the horns. Leave the rest.
You don’t belong here. kid. Go home.
This is my home.
Is this yours?
Put it down!
Or you're dead.
PRESENT DAY
Welcome home.
You stayed under
the radar as usual.
Call me when you need me again.
Sergei. it is your
father. Come home.
I miss you. I am sorry for
everything that has happened.
I'm just kidding.
It's your brother.
I texted you. Where
have you been?
No. You still hiding
out in the woods. huh?
Am I gonna see
you for my birthday?
Call me back.
Get this shit on the truck!
Come on!
Let's get 'em up.
Who is this?
This is private property.
to lock up before you leave.
Move!
and only take the horns?
Because we can.
Because you can?
Out of the way. There's
six of us and only one of you.
There's six of you now.
I ain't got time for
this. I've got deadlines.
Hey. did you hear him?
What the fuck?
Go. go!
Mr. Tagland. I apologize.
This guy. he came
out of nowhere.
A crazy local
or... I don't know.
But I took care of it. He
won't be bothering us anymore.
In a moment. you won't be
bothered by much of anything.
How did you...
Where's Mr. Tagland?
Oh. you're standing in him.
Found this. Interesting read.
You're a poacher. Mr. Tagland.
He hires poachers.
But these names? Drugs.
weapons. trafficking...
- No. no. no. I...
- What's your name?
André.
André who?
The men in that book.
they're the ones you want.
They're the ones in charge.
I can help you find them.
I don't need your help.
But I will be adding
these names to my list.
André who?
Lavigne.
Put it all in a
pecking order. André.
Oh. found you.
And now. today's headlines.
Crusading London
prosecutor Samantha Hodges
was gunned down last
week in broad daylight.
following a string of vicious attacks
targeting law enforcement and the judiciary.
Memorial services
will be held later today.
I met Samantha when
I first moved to London.
She was a mentor...
...a dear friend.
and one of the fiercest fighters
for justice this city has ever known.
We all know who did this.
Samantha dared to stand in Semyon Chorny's way
and hold him accountable.
And for that act of courage.
she lost her life.
This system's broken.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Shit.
I didn't mean to scare you.
You did.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Did you know her well?
Actually. I didn't
know her at all.
Well. then thank you
for the condolences.
Calypso.
I think this belongs to you.
You're...
You're the boy.
- No. you were... You were...
- I was.
For three minutes.
Would have been a whole lot
longer if you hadn't been there.
Those were my
grandmother's cards.
I actually still carry
the deck with me.
So why'd you give it to me?
I guess I thought you needed it.
Is this all you had to go on?
How'd you find me?
Hunting people down
is sort of my thing.
Hunting?
Do you know who did this?
Yeah. I do.
They gonna get him?
Probably not.
What would you say if I told you...
...I already did.
Crime Boss Killed in Prison Cell
Seven Killings: is there a pattern?
Cartel leader poisoned on private yacht
WHO IS THE HUNTER?
A tiger's tooth?
I use whatever
tools are available.
Why would you do that?
Wasn't he responsible
for killing your friend?
Look. I've been trying to
find you for a very long time.
This is my way of saying
thank you for saving my life.
I didn't ask you
to murder anyone.
I'm a lawyer.
But that bastard got
what he deserved.
I know who your father is.
You're like him?
A gangster?
No.
I grew up watching my
father put evil into the world.
The old man had
it all figured out.
I was supposed to follow in his footsteps
and take over the family business.
But something happened to me
that day you found me.
So. I got as far away
from my father as I could.
And now I do what I can
to get rid of people like him.
So you're the hunter?
That's just what they
call me in the press.
I prefer Kraven.
Kraven?
With a K.
The only people who have
heard that name are dead now.
Then I guess I'll just
have to watch my back.
So do you live here?
I live about as far away as you
can possibly get from this place.
And my brother does.
We. um...
I wasn't always there for
him. so I check in when I can.
What about you? How
did you end up here?
Some days I'm not so sure.
Um...
My parents were lawyers.
so that's what I did.
I was in the D.A.'s
office in New York for
seven years until I
couldn't take it anymore.
Sometimes the law can
get in the way of justice.
It can.
Now I'm in London. at one of
the biggest law firms in Europe.
I know where you work. You're one of the
best investigative lawyers in that place.
I also know...
all your clients
aren't exactly angels.
That's true.
So what are you really getting
down from behind that desk?
I have a list.
A list?
There are other ways to do
what you set out to do. Calypso.
Well. you're gonna need a lawyer. or worse.
if you keep messing around in this world.
What about a partnership?
From inside that firm. you can find
people I can't. and then I can do what...
Yeah. I get it.
I'll think about it.
Kraven.
And a little friendly advice.
If you keep going after
the names on that list.
people you care about are gonna get hurt.
Ryazha.
We need to talk about this.
Yes. we go again?
Go. go!
Do you hear me?
Ryazha. come on. give it here.
Are you going to make me beg?
You know I don't beg.
You think I'm weak?
Ryazha!
It's okay. Rajinka.
Yes. you're my Ryazhuska.
Papa loves you.
Papa forgives you.
One more thing.
Semyon Chorny was
killed in his prison cell.
Who got to him?
They're saying
it was the hunter.
Faster than a cheetah.
cunning as a fox.
More ferocious than a tiger.
Tell me. do you think
this hunter actually exists?
Be a load of bollocks.
But then again. I
hear he's got a list.
Once you're on it.
you never come off.
And there's a good
chance you're on it.
If he is real. he can be found.
I'll do some digging.
Wait.
Chorny's operations
are up for grabs now.
Set to meet...
his top three guys.
Your boss. Semyon
Chorny. is dead.
I intend to assume control
of his asset transactions.
One of you will be my partner.
Who's it going to be?
Best pitch wins.
He calls himself "Rhino."
He doesn't look like a Rhino to me.
But don't you want to know...
why they call me the Rhino?
Why do it to yourself?
I have to see who
they're dealing with.
Get rid of him.
Oh. it's okay. Roger.
It's okay.
You can put your guns away.
If I want you dead. I only
have to raise my... Don't!
Whenever a rhino sees his
opportunity. he doesn't hesitate.
He charges in and takes it.
So. I'll ask one more time.
Which one of you is
going to be my partner?
Hell of a pitch.
We have a winner.
My son. Dmitri.
This next one is for you. Papa.
♪ The way you wear your hat... ♪
it does for me.
He knows I like Tony Bennett.
You like Tony Bennett?
I don't trust anyone who
doesn't like Tony Bennett.
He can do anyone.
He's like a chameleon.
He's assassins.
If they can get
your boss in cage...
I think we all need
to take precautions.
I understand.
Come closer.
Johnny. he is gone.
That makes your operations
become vulnerable.
I can offer you security. distribution.
and most critically. peace of mind.
Sounds good. I'm on board.
Just like that.
You don't want
to think about it.
Order has to be restored.
The sooner the better.
You have already
done deal. didn't you?
Who is?
The Rhino sends his regards.
Get up.
You're hit.
Are you all right. Papa?
Look at what they
have done to my club.
I get attacked on my own ground.
And who do I have to thank me?
My son. the piano player?
Go on. Hit me. Fight me.
I need fighters. not coward.
You won't even defend yourself.
The Kravinoff hit failed.
All of our guys are dead.
Nikolai is a tough old
bear. He won't go quietly.
I found this slipped
under my door.
Nikolai Kravinoff's son.
Sergei. is the hunter?
But what is this Kraven?
Apparently. that's
what he calls himself.
This can't be real.
Is it?
Not sure.
Put the foreigner on this.
He is a bit of a freak. but he's been
obsessed with the hunter for years.
Maybe he can figure out
what the fuck is going on.
What are you doing?
It’s okay.
killed Semyon Chorney.
Turn around.
You don't have access here
because I'm not from around anywhere.
One...
Two...
Three.
Goodbye now.
Surprise!
Jesus! Sergei!
You scared the shit out of me.
Happy birthday. baby brother.
I love you. man.
What are we gonna do. huh?
Well. you're not wearing that.
- Great. Let's stay in.
- What?
It's my birthday.
On your birthday. we can go to the petting
zoo. or wherever it is you let loose.
But tonight. this.
What makes you
think I can fit in that?
This is too big on me.
so it'll be perfect for you.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Pleasure. Nice
perfume. by the way.
Thanks. but I'm not
actually wearing any.
She was gonna
find out soon enough.
Papa was sitting right here.
It all happened so fast.
You find out what you're
made of in a moment like that.
I'm a coward.
No. you're not a coward.
It's natural to feel fear.
That's just your instinct. huh?
Why don't we get to
choose who we are?
Why do I have to be me?
I need to be strong. fearless.
I would run towards the bullets.
I wouldn't crumble to the ground.
Why would you want to
be anybody but yourself?
So he could respect me for once.
Papa's a criminal. so
what good is his respect?
You act like you don't
care what he thinks.
that you're above it.
that he can't touch you.
Well. he can.
He made you hate people.
I don't hate people.
I hate what people do.
but I don't hate people.
I guess then Papa was
right about one thing.
Yeah.
Man should be the only
animal that is dreaded.
I'm glad I didn't miss the party.
How could I stay away and miss
the chance and see both my sons?
Dmitri.
For you.
I don't expect you to give
me a hug. but a handshake?
Dasha.
I just came for one toast.
To honor Dmitri.
On his big day.
Pour.
Pour for men.
Not for boys.
Come on. Sergei.
To the Kravinoffs.
Maybe we'll learn someday to
forget the past and imagine the future.
Together.
As a family.
To your health.
There we go.
Are you okay?
Sergei.
Huh?
I know why you come every year.
Because you feel guilty
for leaving me with him.
I forgive you.
For...
...everything.
I'm sorry.
Sergei! Sergei!
Hold that. will ya?
Please?
Buddy?
Penthouse. please.
I tried to hold it for you.
No. you didn't.
This?
It's my travel knife.
Use it for work.
What you do for work. exactly?
I hunt.
People.
Dmitri!
Please! Please!
Let go!
Wait. wait. stop. please! Wait. wait!
We can figure this out.
Put him under.
There he is!
Lose him!
Get the fuck out of the way!
Fuck!
Go!
Faster!
Dmitri!
It's bulletproof. idiot!
Inside and out!
Get him off!
Go. go!
Dima!
Hello. sir. Is there
something I can help you with?
A towel. maybe?
Thank you so much.
Appreciate it.
Sir.
I think you left your shoes in the lobby.
I'm pretty sure I did.
Why don't we go down
and have a look together?
There are enough vaults
in the world. then. my friend.
Brian. everything's
fine. He's a client.
What the hell. Sergei?
I told you I'd think
about your offer.
You cannot come
in here like this.
This is my place of business.
They got my brother.
Who got your brother?
There were four of them.
Took him from his place.
So you saw them?
There was this one guy.
Dark hair. brown eyes. he's
got a scar under his left eye.
Sounded Turkish.
Jesus.
You spoke to them?
Not exactly.
There was some
screaming involved.
Okay.
Let's get into it. then.
I should have
been there for him.
I couldn't sleep. so...
I left and went
for a walk and...
We're gonna find him.
Okay?
I'm gonna do what I do.
Get us a name.
And then you are
going to do what you do.
And we will get him back.
I'm looking for a mercenary who
just ran a kidnapping op in London.
Wound-shaped scar
under his left eye.
Smokes Turkish cigarettes.
Probably a national.
Find him.
Sergei.
Who are they?
They would not say.
But you know. don't you?
My list of enemies is long.
Look what they did to him.
How much do they want?
20 million.
In 48 hours.
Pay them.
It is complicated.
No. it's not. It's very simple.
You have the money
and he's your son.
This is not about money.
This is about power.
If I pay...
I am weak.
If I show weakness...
I begin to lose everything
I've spent lifetime building.
A lifetime building what?
You're a drug dealer.
You don't get to
do that anymore.
Dmitri is innocent.
You let him die. his
blood is on your hands.
On my hands?
My hands?
I did not abandon him.
You abandoned him.
You.
He was dead the
moment he was taken.
Whether I pay or not.
No. you don't know that.
Yes. I know.
Because that is what I would do.
You're despicable.
Of course I want him back.
I want both my sons back.
Some legend you've become.
Wake up!
Take these.
Antibiotics.
I can't have you
dying on me. can I?
It's good.
Omer Ozdemir.
He's holed up in a monastery
in the outskirts of Ankara.
Thank you.
You can thank me by
never calling me again.
We'll see.
How'd it go?
She took it.
Of course she took it.
But did she believe you?
Yeah. she trusts me.
Which is why I want double
what your boss promised.
Double?
Why not triple?
What game are you playing?
One.
Two.
Three.
It's done.
Get ready.
The hunter is on his way.
Sergei. the man you're
looking for is Omer Ozdemir.
I found an old monastery
in his family name in Turkey.
And that is where
you'll find your brother.
Thank you for this.
Alright. Ellie. let's go.
NORTHERN TURKEY
Thank you.
It's him.
He's there.
Where is Dmitri?
Where is he?
Drop me.
And you'll never
find your brother...
Kraven.
How do you know my name?
Who set me up?
Who took my brother?
The Rhino.
He's killed us both now.
Run!
Who are you?
Does one of you have an evidence bag?
I left mine in the car.
What's that?
This is crushed rosary piece.
The man who did
this knows his toxins.
One.
Two.
Three.
What are you doing?
Goodbye now.
That's enough. Ryazha.
I'm very sorry
about your finger.
Collateral damage.
Cut him free.
We met once.
On your father's hunting trip.
I don't remember.
No. you wouldn't.
My hair was different.
You were very young.
Me?
I never forgot.
So have you spoken to my father?
Has he agreed to pay?
No.
Nikolai Kravinoff was
never going to hand over
20 million dollars to
get his bastard son back.
You're an accident. Dmitri.
You came into this
world as an accident.
And you came into my
possession as an accident.
So can I go?
Those men who took you.
They weren't there for you.
They were there
for your brother.
Sergei?
Both of you went in.
But when my guys got
up there... he'd vanished.
As he always does.
So I took you.
I got lucky.
Why would you ever want Sergei?
He never hurt anyone.
You really don't know. do you?
Know what?
Wait for the end.
That's the best part.
Kraven?
Apparently that's what
he calls himself now.
You think my brother
Sergei is the Hunter?
The Hunter is a story.
A fable to put
fear into criminals.
Clearly you didn't know
your brother very well.
What do you mean. didn't?
Kraven had a list.
Once you're on it.
you never come off.
So I went after him first.
Let me record this.
We've got Kraven.
I don't know about that.
Hello?
Calypso. it's me.
The whole thing was
a trap. The Rhino?
He knows who I am.
He'll be after you next.
Sergei. what are you... shit.
There are five guys
walking into my building
right now who do not
look like they belong here.
You need to get
out of there now.
Get to the cargo terminal and stance it.
I'll have someone meet you there.
I call this my feed bag.
It's a mixture of medications
to manage my condition.
What happened to you?
I was underestimated too.
In and out of hospitals. they
never quite knew what was wrong.
I knew I would never
have your father's respect.
Or anyone else's.
Until I was strong.
I tried everything.
And then...
I found someone.
In New York.
A biochemist.
A professor. Miles Warren.
He was developing a
procedure to increase strength.
Tenfold.
I signed up on the spot.
My skin. it started to harden.
I was indestructible.
Like a rhino.
But the pain...
It was too much.
I think there is an animal
in each one of us. Dmitri.
I'm taking over
your father's territory.
I want you to be my partner.
The Kravinoff name
still opens a lot of doors.
And you'll finally get the
consideration you deserve.
You're right.
I have been underestimated.
My whole life.
But if you think I'm going
to betray my family...
You're wrong.
Boss.
The boys haven't checked in.
I can't reach them.
Kraven is alive.
Hey. Bart!
Alpha team. Bravo team.
He's here.
Cute.
Will your trick still work when I
remove your eyeballs from your head?
Relax.
Sorry I got you
wrapped up in all this.
Any word on Dmitri?
Not yet.
Three of my sources have gone
offline while tracking the rhino's plane.
I don't like the feel of this.
I don't like this at all.
So. what is this place?
My mother's family
used to own this property.
Well. it's really the only
thing I have left from her.
What is happening right now?
We're being hunted.
By who?
You don't hunt me!
Yeah. get pissed.
What are you gonna
do? Come on. show me!
I've seen her around since she was a cub.
but she's a lot bigger than I remember.
Oh. you're a goddamn
lunatic. I swear.
Oh. you just
figured that out now?
I know I hired you for the job.
But who is Kraven to you?
Why the obsession?
My mentor was one of
the greatest assassins who ever lived.
He taught me everything I know.
He was like a brother to me.
Maybe you knew him?
I've heard of him.
He was murdered.
One man made it
inside and cut his throat.
Kraven?
So I traveled the world.
Followed him wherever he went.
But Kraven is nature's
perfect predator.
He has no known weaknesses.
But you found one.
And I know how to exploit it.
Well. get to the part
where I start to give a shit.
These are eastern
Siberian rosary peas.
A rare species.
I found their residue on a
poison in the monastery.
These peas are only native
to a specific region in Siberia.
That's where we'll find them.
Oh. careful with that.
Actually. I'm pretty good
with one of these things.
Archery. At summer camp.
Fig wart.
Wood avens.
Tribulus.
Rosary peas.
You seem to know your stuff.
They'll kill you.
Or save you.
Nature's funny like that.
What are you trying to do here?
Tell me about this.
It was my grandmother's.
We were on safari
visiting her that day.
I've been trying to figure out
what was in here for years.
My grandmother
was kind of a... mystic.
She had a lot of
crazy stuff around.
My parents didn't like to talk about it.
but she was a very powerful woman.
She said it would heal
whoever drank it in...
undreamed of ways.
I was... I was just a kid.
I didn't know what
it would actually do.
This saved my life.
Did it?
Trust me. it changed me.
Exactly.
Look at what you became.
I need to know...
what was in here.
And if you can get any more.
No.
She died not long after that
trip. and I never saw her again.
I heard back from
one of my sources.
The rhino's on the move.
We should know more very soon.
I knew you'd be good at this.
Sergei... we're
gonna get Dmitri back.
But is all of this
really worth it?
Calypso. I was made to do this.
I'm the greatest
hunter on this planet.
It's undeniable.
There's nobody I
can't track down.
Nobody I can't beat.
There's nobody who
can even touch me.
So. no.
Why would I want to stop?
It's called karma.
She catches up to you.
Not me.
I'm faster than she is.
But Dmitri wasn't.
Interesting piece.
It's gonna take more
than a gun to kill Kraven.
I find this formula that was developed
by MI6 to be particularly effective.
May I?
It first brings down
your darkest nightmares.
then paralysis of
your vital organs.
before a most violent death.
I like your style.
Only one person has this number.
Dima. where are you?
Sergei. I'm sorry
they made me call you.
Dmitri.
I'm afraid not.
But now you know he is alive.
What do you want?
A life.
Without looking
over my shoulder.
You have two choices.
I know you hate your
father as much as I do.
So. you and I.
and young Dmitri here.
we work together.
You could be my partners.
Or I kill you and burn...
Okay then.
Now we go hunt the hunter.
Spread out.
Bring me his body.
Or don't come back.
Ryazha
Where is he?
He's already here.
Shit! Look out!
Amateurs.
So embarrassing for us.
Do it.
Start the run.
Fire in the hole!
You gotta be kidding!
The spiders!
The hallucinations are just beginning.
Are you seeing your worst nightmare?
One...
Two...
Three.
As the poison makes its way to your spinal cord...
...you'll begin to lose all motor functions.
motor functions. motor functions...
Then it's fixation. fixation. fixation...
So you're the legend.
The myth.
Well. look at you now.
You're just a man.
You give him hell. Kraven.
Honestly. I thought that would be harder.
It's done.
But the brother's still out there
Go find him.
Let's go.
One...
Two...
Three. motherfucker.
Goodbye. Kraving the Hunter
Sergei!
Can't catch a break.
Can you. mate?
Legends don't die.
Now get the fuck up. Kraven.
I knew you had more of that.
Well. forgive me for not trusting a lunatic
with my family's deepest legacy.
Get up.
Okay.
Well. that must be some summer camp.
You're not the only one with secrets.
Don't make me regret this.
It's over.
Raven's dead.
What a day.
Put him in the car.
Who knows maybe Nikolai will pay
now that he has only one son left.
Does anyone else see what I'm seeing?
Kraven!
Gosh. you're really heavy.
Sergei...
My father was right about one thing.
You are nothing.
The video of me.
How did you get it?
Who sent it?
How is it that even the great hunter
can't see what was always right
in front of him?
No.
- He deserves to die.
- And he will.
But Dmitri. it's not you.
I wish...
I wish I never met you. Kravinoff.
NORTHERN RUSSIA
Sergei.
How did you find me?
I'm a hunter.
It's what we do.
You sent the video and
told the rhino who I was.
Did you really think
father would not recognize
the actions of his own son?
An assassin who uses all the
methods of animals of the jungle?
You of all people should recognize
and appreciate the beauty of the trap I set.
The Rhino is coming for you.
You weren't strong enough
to fight him off by yourself. huh?
Exactly.
But my son?
My real son.
Kraven.
No one is stronger.
And I knew you would
not go after him for me.
So I sent him after you.
Some trap.
I mean. Dmitri could have died
but that's the price
of doing business. right?
No. no. no. no. no.
Because I know...
...you would not let anything
happen to our precious Dmitri.
- Our empire is secure.
- So what now...
...papa? Do we...
...forget about the past?
Imagine a future. together?
As a family.
Sergei...
...where are you going?
I could have come for you.
Years ago.
But I didn't.
After everything you've done...
All the pain you put in the world...
...you are my father.
I still am.
Sit.
Never fear death.
Isn't that what you taught me?
ONE YEAR LATER
Happy birthday. Dima.
It is a happy birthday.
First one in a long time.
And that's thanks to you. Sergei.
Oh. come on.
Or Kraven. should I say.
What do I call you now? Mr. Kraven?
- You know who I am.
- I know you.
That was. um...
...hell.
What I went through.
But it also freed me.
I feel almost born again.
I found a doctor in New York.
A little unorthodox. I must admit.
But he really helped me. I mean...
Changed me.
- How so?
- Hang on a sec.
Since when did you have
friends in the brava. huh?
Well. I have business. with lots of people.
Business? I thought you said
you wanted to sell papa's assets
and get out of the business.
- I changed my mind.
- Dima...
I didn't pull your ass out the fire
so you can become a man like a father.
Are you serious?
You put my ass in that fire.
You're a man just like our father.
No. I'm nothing like him.
- I have a code.
- And you're different than him.
I'm better than him.
You're saying you're not better
than him. you're worse.
How did papa die again?
A hunting accident.
Was it? Don't lie to me.
You think you have some kind of honor. huh?
Some kind of code.
Bullshit.
You're just another man
hunting for a trophy.
Hey.
Dmitri.
You should see the look on your face.
You know me.
I've always been a chameleon.
That's the one thing I was ever good at.
Who is this doctor?
What did he do to you?
You want me to be weak.
So then you can be strong...
...but I'm strong now.
I can be whoever I wanna be.
The Rhino is gone. dad is gone.
It's all just there. for the taking.
I'm gonna take it.
You know I can't let you do that.
Go home. Kraven.
Dad left you something.
Sergei.
Each of us has path to walk
Embrace who you really are
and you will have the strength to walk it.
You are more than my child.
You are me.
And I am you.
We are hunters.
The greatest the world has ever known.